♪ We
♪ Are the Crystal
♪ Gems
♪ We'll always save the day
Steven: ♪ And if you think
we can't, we'll ♪
♪ Always find a way
♪ That's why the people
♪ Of this world
♪ Believe in
♪ Garnet
♪ Amethyst
♪ And Pearl
And Steven!
洋葱头显然非常高兴
Onion sure was having a phenomenal time
和史蒂文在沙发上蹦跶
jumping with Steven on his couch.
但蹦了两个小时后
But after two hours of jumping,
他决定是时候结束了
he decided that it was time to perhaps stop
然后去做点别的？
and do something else?
啊，洋葱头打算吃点零食
Ah, so Onion decided he wanted a snack.
而且他知道他可以随意
And he knew he could help himself
享用史蒂文厨房里的任何东西
to anything in Steven's kitchen.
包括史蒂文的限量版薯片...
[ Sighs ] Including Steven's favorite limited edition chips.
洋葱头闻了闻薯片
Onion smelled the chip,
在鉴赏那极致气息
savoring its delicious aroma.
但没有零食能满足
But no snack could satisfy his hunger...
他对潜力的渴望
for power.
看来你爸爸回家了？
Oh, looks like you're dad's home, huh?
我猜本集“洋葱头的传说”
I guess this round of "Onion Tales"
该结束了。
has come to an end.
再见！
See ya!
结语
Epilogue --
洋葱头不得不面对孤独
things get a little lonely for Onion,
不认识任何同龄伙伴
not knowing any other kids his age.
但好在他有史蒂文
But luckily he had his friend Steven
一个愿意花时间陪伴“留守儿童”的人
who would kindly donate some time to a youth in need.
来啦！
Coming!
噢，洋葱头
Oh, Onion.
又想找人玩玩？
Need someone to hang out with again?
进来吧
Come on in.
啊哈
Oh, I see.
洋葱头想进门，但在门外被拦住了，
Onion wanted to come in, but he paused in the doorway.
他需要拖鞋，但不知道怎么脱
He needed to take his shoes off, but he didn't know how.
你想去别的地方？
You want to go somewhere else?
你好，维达利亚！你好，黄鳍-噫-噫
Hi, Vidalia! Hi, Yellowta-a-a-ail.
我们刚跑过了你家，洋葱头！
W-We just ran past your house, Onion!
你要带我去哪？
Where are you taking me?
我们在哪？
Where are we?
我都不知带你能吹口哨！
I didn't know you could whistle like that!
有人吗？
Is someone there?
鹰嘴豆
Garbanzo!
啊，你们是很么人？
Aah! Who are you?
你们缓慢怪异的步伐让我很不舒服！
Your slow and eerie approach is making me uncomfortable!
啊啊啊啊！
Aah!
洋葱头，快跑！
Onion, run!
看来史蒂文-宇宙该退场了
Looks like it's curtains for Steven Universe.
洋葱头，啊？
Onion, huh?
你认识这些人吗，洋葱头?
Uh, do you know these guys, Onion?
噢，他们是你的朋友！
Oh, they're your friends!
呃，我的名字是史蒂文
Uh, my name's Steven.
鹰嘴豆
Garbanzo.
我猜，你是鹰嘴豆？
I guess, you're Garbanzo?
考虑到你以豆子起名
Since you're named after a bean
那你背上的宝宝一定叫...
then the baby on your back must be...
花豆？
Pinto?
你的名字是...
And your name is...
噢，笋瓜！
Oh, Squash!
在我左边是...
And to my left, we have...
弹弓？
Slingshot?
呃...锅盖头？
Uh, pot hat?
我不太清楚...
Uh, I don't know.
特-昂-汤？
S-- S-S-Soup
呼～很高兴认识你们！
Whew!  It's nice to meet all of you.
多么温馨的迎接！
What a warm welcome.
嘿，我钱包！
H-Hey, that's my wallet!
洋葱头，我一直以为你是个孤独的小男孩
Onion, this whole time I thought you were just a lonely boy.
但你有一屋子朋友
But you have a whole pantry of friends!
谢谢你带我来这里
Thanks for bringing me here.
鹰嘴豆
Garbanzo.
酷！一个肥皂箱做的Derby Car（手工制作的玩具车）
Cool! A soap-box derby car thing!
我能帮一把吗？
Can I lend you all a hand?
鹰嘴豆
Garbanzo.
这安全吗？
Is that safe?
鹰嘴豆
Garbanzo!
看起来超棒！
This looks amazing!
我做的下吗？
Is there enough room for me?
好吧，出发！
All right, let's roll!
居然能爬陡坡！
It even goes up steep hills!
飘～
Swerve-y!
鹰嘴豆
Garbanzo!
呃...发生了什么？
Uh... What's going on?
等等！他不会有事吧？就只是撞了一下！
Wait! He's gonna be okay, right? It was just a little spill!
这都是真的吗？
Is this... really happening?
噢，花豆...我不知道该说什么...
Oh, Pinto... I don't know what to say.
这一切发生的太突然了
This is all happened so suddenly.
我-我去找救护人员！
I-I'll call a medical professional!
真是个奇迹！花豆有治愈...能力？
It's a miracle! Pinto has healing pow...ers?
为什么你又捅我，又眨眼，就像这都是...
W-Why'd you nudge me and wink like this was all...
套路？
a big joke?
--我明白了。嘿，这都是套路
I -- I get it. Heh. G-Good joke.
你们...你们真的骗过我了。
Hmm. Y'all -- Y'all really got me with that.
哇，真是个肥大的风衣！
Whoa! That is a huge trench coat!
你们打算拿来做什么？
What're you gonna do with that?
你们打算伪装成大人？
You're gonna pretend to be grown?
我能跟你们一起吗？
Can I pretend with you?
天，我们看起来太成年了！
Man, we look so grown up!
我们先做什么？
What should we do first?
买辆车？出入豪华旅馆(？
Buy a car? Stay in a fancy hotel?
投票？
Vote?
嘿，那不是行李山姆吗？
Hey, is that Suitcase Sam?
你觉得如果我们突然撞见他，他会对我们说“先生”？
You think if we bump into him, he'll call us "sir?"
那会很有趣！
That would be funny!
哦？我们是这么做吗？
Oh, are we doing it?
你好，行李山姆先生！
Hello, Suitcase Sam, sir!
是我，你的忠实顾客，成人先生！
It is I, your faithful customer, Mister Mature Man.
啊！
Aah!
为什么？
W-Why'd you do that?
天...
Man...
我一直以为当我们没在一起玩时
I always thought when we weren't hanging out,
你只是一个人坐在栈道上，洋葱头
you were just sitting alone on the boardwalk, Onion.
这一切从什么时候开始的？
How long has this been going on?
怎么了？只是在土里画画？
What's going on over here? Just drawing in the dirt, Eh?
这很好，一点也不吓人
That's cool, that's not creepy.
对不对，汤汤？
Right, Soup?
呃...好吧
Uh...okay.
我应该,,,噢，好吧
What should I-- Oh, okay.
这是...个比赛吗？
Is this...a race?
你,,,你们在赛虫？
Y-You're racing bugs?
有意思！
That's fun!
坚持住啊! 你能做到的! 不要停!
Come on!You can do it!
呼！我赢了！
Whoo-hoo! I won!
给我的？谢谢！
For me? Thank you!
什么？你们想让我...
What? You want me to...
但...但它赢了啊！
But -- But he won!
我...我...
I...I...
我做不到！
I can't do it!
虫子也许很怪，但我不想杀死它！
Bugs may be weird, but I don't want to kill one!
对不起，我得回家了!
I'm sorry. I'm going home!
还好！
All right. Whew!
不要再有奇怪的朋友了，我看看...
No more weirdo friends. Let's see...
我赌我亲亲的康妮有空
I bet my best friend Connie is free.
嘿，康妮！是我，史蒂文！
Hey, Connie! It's me, Steven!
我--我在想你是否有...
I -- I was wondering if you --
呃...不，并没有什么任务。我只想和你在一起～
Um, no, th-there's no mission, I wanted to hang out!
你要进行返校采购？
You gotta do back to school shopping?
噢，好吧
Oh, okay.
替我向铅笔们问好。
Say hi to the pencils for me.
好吧，我想佩迪应该愿意出来玩玩
Well, I bet Peedee wants to hang.
[我没法出来玩。暑期最后加班]
算了
No big deal.
总得有人有空吧？
I-I'm sure someone else is free.
看来没有同龄好伙伴的孤独少男...
Looks like the lonely boy with no friends his age
其实是...
was actually...
史蒂文
Steven.
不，洋葱头!我想静静！
No, Onion! Just leave me alone!
你不用再陪我玩了
You don't have to play with me anymore.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?!
不，洋葱头!
No, Onion!
洋葱头，听我说！
Onion, listen!
我想通了！
I figured it out!
你和我玩的唯一原因
The only reason you hang out with me
是你同情我，对吧？
is 'cause you feel bad for me, isn't it?
你不需要撒谎来安慰我！
You don't have to lie to me to protect my feelings!
那些在树林中的孩子们？
Those kids out there in the woods?
你们了解彼此，甚至无需言语！
You understand each other and you don't even talk!
他们是你真正的朋友！
They're your real friends.
所以走吧！
So just go!
我不需要你可怜我！
I don't need you to pity me.
这是我一个人能做的
That's the one thing I can do by myself.
嘿，你是...你是比赛的获胜者
Hey, you're -- you're the winner of the bug race.
等等！洋葱头！我对不起！
Wait! Onion! I'm sorry!
洋葱头，等等我！
Onion, wa-a-ait!
伙计们，对不起！都怪我！
Guys, I'm sorry! It was me!
我才是那个孤独的人！我--
I was the lonely boy! I --
嘿，到底怎么了？
Hey, what's going on?
等等...
Wait...
你们是...
are you guys...
要走吗？
leaving?
对不起之前表现的非常怪异！
I'm sorry about being weirded out before!
你们没必要走啊！
You don't have to leave!
噢
Oh.
我--我知道了
I-I get it now.
你们只在夏天到beach city来
You guys only come to Beach City during the summer months.
现在秋天来了
And since the fall is starting,
你们该准备回家了
it must be time for you to go home.
我不知道该说什么。我--
I don't know what to say. I --
噢！谢谢你们让我一起玩！
Aww! Thanks for letting me hangout with you guys...
你们都很棒！
You're all swell!
再见！我永远不会忘记你们的！
Goodbye! I'll never forget you all!
所以...那就是你为什么那么想让我回到这里
So, that's why you wanted me to come back here so much.
这是你最后的机会
This was your last chance
和你所有的朋友在一起
to have all your friends in the same place.
噢...洋葱头非常伤心
Uh... Onion felt really sad
因为他夏天的伙伴都走了
about his summer friends leaving.
但是...
But...
他又好过了一点
then, he started to feel a little better.
他想起了与朋友的所有美好时光
He remembered all the great times he had with his friends
和一起搞的事情！
and all the cool stuff they did together!
暑假再临前
And until next summer,
他还有好朋友史蒂文一起玩
he had his pal Steven to hangout with...
如果他愿意
i-if he wants to.
噢...伙计...
Aww, buddy...
Summer of Steven 放送完毕！终于追上进度。。【倒地